<tweet>
	<author>ironhelmetgames</author>
	<post>Building circular maps for NP2 today. Have feedback?
https://t.co/hm2r66sCGJ</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>rockpapershot</author>
	<post>Via THQ, Nordic Games got Red Faction and Darksiders and Supreme Commander and Titan Quest and and and http://t.co/sM8tM6FLI1</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>steam_games</author>
	<post>Pre-Purchase Now - GRID 2: #PrePurchase http://t.co/bAxNB1XV1A</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>eliderz</author>
	<post>RT @PrepKidProblems: Their Ralph Lauren is from the outlet *gasp* #prepkidproblem</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>Sheriberri94</author>
	<post>In exactly 2 weeks from tomorrow I will be done with my freshman year of college. #surreal #thrilled #bringonsophomoreyear</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>ManuelNvro</author>
	<post>My youngest sister just racked me for the first time, should I be proud or scared?</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>bamboozledd</author>
	<post>RT @CancelDatB_tch: Bops be like: 

#oomf &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;
#oomf &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;
#oomf &gt;&gt</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>bamboozledd</author>
	<post>Glitter is the herpes of craft supplies.</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>Nick_Hanemann</author>
	<post>RT @ActuallyBrandon: Kind of like Tom Hanks in "Big" except more Drake.</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>I guess they didn't have "real" lesbian characters on TV pre-1997, but I get the sense that Ivanova was supposed to be. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Marcus: "I sense in [Ivanova] a key unturned." Man, that's quite a metaphor. By key you mean? #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Lieutenant failed the interview, and his non-chance with Ivanova. Now Marcus is talking about boning her. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Oh no I wasn't ready for this horrible fremdshamen moment. I don't watch shows like that. Just get back to space laser battles plz. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Y'ever been on what you thought was a date but wasn't? Or what you thought wasn't but was? I empathise with the bumbling lieutenant. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>The new lieutenant thinks Ivanova is asking him out for a booty call, and he appears literally terrified. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Can you imagine Marcus singing lead on a yacht rock album? Sea breeze in his auburn locks. I can see it. #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>sixohsix</author>
	<post>Marcus' haircut has not aged well. It's like my dad's 70's haircut. Or my haircut. Uh, it's great, I mean! #B5S03</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>bamboozledd</author>
	<post>RT @ThatsSarcasm: Swerve http://t.co/Z4piU5yjHs</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>Sheriberri94</author>
	<post>RT @Josephgee93: #MentionAFollowerThatCanGetIt @Sheriberri94</post>
</tweet>
<tweet>
	<author>bamboozledd</author>
	<post>RT @Blackbarbie_Ree: God is soooo good to me </post>
</tweet>
